https://qcaspas.com/privacy-policy

We Ship World Wide!
0
Recently added item(s)
×
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Search
My Account
My Cart (0)
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Hot Tub ModelsView All Hot Tub ModelsBuild A SpaStar SeriesPeridot SeriesPerformance SeriesMajestic SeriesBenefitsHealth & WellnessLifestyleFitnessSocialFeaturesShellCabinetPatented HydrotherapyFiltrationInsulation & EfficiencyLED LightingSound SystemsOzonatorBromine Salt SystemStainless Steel JetsHard CoversAbout QCA SpasWhy Choose QCA?Construction & InnovationEquipmentWarranty & SafetyMade in the U.S.A.SupportSpa & Water MaintenanceWarranty RegistrationParts, Accessories, & ChemicalsBecome a DealerOwner's ManualsQCA Spas Product Catalogs
Home
/
QCA Spas Privacy Policy
QCA Spas Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy!
Use of your Personal Information
When accessing our Site, www.qcaspas.com may collect certain information from you during your visit. How we will handle information about you depends on how you interact with our website. If during your visit to our site you read or download information, we may collect and store any of the following information about you including:
1. The name of the domain from which you access the Internet 2. The date and time you accessed our site 3. The IP internet address you used to link to our site.
If you identify yourself by sending us an e-mail containing personal information, then the information collected will be used to respond to your message but never sold to third parties. You may receive followup emails that you can opt-out of at any time. We may use software programs to view the number of visitors to different sections of our website which aids us in identifying system performance or other website issues and treands.
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, www.qcaspas.com uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to non-affiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.
Log Files Like many other websites, www.qcaspas.com uses log files which may include internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, visitor type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP ), date/time stamp of visit, referring/exit pages and analytics as well as to gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information which does not link to any personally identifiable information.
Cookies
www.qcaspas.com may use cookies to store information about visitors preferences in order to customize their web experience.
DoubleClick DART Cookieqcaspas.com does not use Google ads and does not serve ads from the Double Click network anywhere on our site.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
Contact us at support@qcaspas.com with any questions related to this privacy policy.
QCA Spas Inc.  |  1021 State Street, Bettendorf, Iowa 52722  |  563-359-3881  |  888-SAY-SPAS
Proud Makers of
©
QCA Spas, Inc.. All Rights Reserved.
Website designed & hosted by: Computer Team, Inc.
